[Music]
we all share
the same destination
we all work
together as one
in this place there's only one vision
and that's
to be number one
we all have
the right combination
care and quality there's no compromise
doing the very best will be our mission
it's something we need to realize
it's something very special in our eyes
we are
prudential our values mean a lot we are
the people
who will give it all we've got
with a sunny disposition
we can overcome the odds yes
[Music]
take one more step
reach out for
excellence
we'll do whatever it takes to touch the
sky
and we'll help each other reach our
aspirations
[Music]
we know that we can do it if we strive
to be our potential
[Applause]
our values mean a lot we are the people
[Music]
yes we have a valid reason to believe
we are number one
[Music]